Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Geology, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records
  - Student records, 1948-1967
    - Crosley, Perry Arliss (Box 6)
    - Cross, Robt. Roy (Box 6)
    - Crowder, D. F. (Box 6)
    - Cruikshank, R.C. (Box 6)
    - Crutcher, John F. (Box 6)
    - Currey, Donald Rusk (Box 6)
    - Curry, Sharon Gay (Box 6)
    - Czamanske, Gerald Kent (Box 6)
    - Dana, Toni (Box 6)
    - Danehy, Edw. A. (Box 6)
    - Darneul, R.L. (Box 6)
    - Davidson, W.R. (Box 6)
    - Davis, Chas. G., Jr. (Box 6)
    - Davis, Gregory A. (Box 6)
    - Day, Paul S. (Box 6)
    - DeGoes, L. L. (Box 6)
    - DeGrys, Antoinette M. (Box 6)
    - DeLara, Fernando (Box 6)
    - DelMar, David Bruce (Box 6)
    - DelSolar, Carlos W. (Box 6)
    - Dobbel, Chas. H. (Box 6)
    - Dobbs, J. Peter (Box 6)
    - Dobbs, Robt. O. (Box 6)
    - Dodge, Frank Chas. (Box 6)
    - Dodge, J. (Box 6)
    - Dohrenwend, Jay Clayton (Box 6)
    - Dolan, H.K. (Box 6)
    - Dole, Hollis M. (Box 6)
    - D'olier, Wm. L. (Box 6)
    - Donath, Fred A. (Box 6)
    - Dort, Wakefield (Box 6)
    - Dougan, Paul Marriott (Box 6)
    - Douglass, R.C. (Box 6)
    - Duncan, David Walter (Box 6)
    - Dundas, Richard C. (Box 6)
    - Dunn, Peter Graves (Box 6)
    - Dyer, Brooks Christy (Box 6)
    - Eberlin, G.D. (Box 6)
    - Eckart, Juan C. (Box 6)
    - Eckert, Frederic Wm. Jr. (Box 6)
    - Eckhart, R.A. (Box 6)
    - Eddington, Ronald C. (Box 6)
    - Edgell, H. Stewart (Box 6)
    - Edwards, Kenneth Lang (Box 6)
    - Eick, Nile C. (Box 6)
    - Eimon, Paul Iver (Box 6)
    - Elliott, Daniel W., Jr. (Box 6)
    - Elliot, Raymond Lynn (Box 6)
    - Emerson, Peter Jan (Box 6)
    - Engebreth, Roald Norman (Box 6)
    - Enos, Paul Portenier (Box 6)
    - Erickson; C.D. (Box 6)
    - Esguerra, Fernando B. (Box 6)
    - Esser, Robt. Worth (Box 6)
    - Estill, W.O. (Box 6)
    - Euribe, Alejandro D. (Box 6)
    - Evans, H. Terry (Box 6)
    - Farmin, J.C. (Box 6)
    - Feltham, Dan Edw. (Box 6)
    - Filley, Edw. C. (Box 6)
    - Findlay, Wm. F. (Box 6)
    - Finley, J.D. (Box 6)
    - Fischer, Warren C. (Box 6)
    - Fish, John L. (Box 6)
    - Fleming, Peter K. (Box 6)
    - Flinter, Basil H. (Box 6)
    - Forbes, C.F. (Box 6)
    - Forbes, D.R. (Box 6)
    - Forkgen, Peter E. (Box 6)
    - Forster, R.W. (Box 6)
    - Foster, John (Box 6)
    - Fox, Geo. S. (Box 6)
    - Frenkel, Robt. Edgar (Box 6)
    - Fricker, Peter (Box 6)
    - Friedman, Philip Martin (Box 6)
    - Fulton, R.B. (Box 6)
    - Funkhouser, John W. (Box 6)
    - Gallagher, Robt. Edw. (Box 7)
    - Gant, Richard A. (Box 7)
    - Gardner, Edwin (Box 7)
    - Garrett, Anthony (Box 7)
    - Garrison, Robt. E. (Box 7)
    - Gervasio, Fruilan C. (Box 7)
    - Gielow, Donald Geo. (Box 7)
    - Gimlett, Jim 1. (Box 7)
    - Giri, Mahen Benigiri (Box 7)
    - Glaze, R.E. (Box 7)
    - Glenn, John Stuart (Box 7)
    - Goddard, Harvey G. (Box 7)
    - Goff, E.A. (Box 7)
    - Gomes Bosco, Joao (Box 7)
    - Gonzales, A. (Box 7)
    - Goodwin, Jas. C. (Box 7)
    - Green, L.A. (Box 7)
    - Green, Thos. S. (Box 7)
    - Greene, Gorelon W. (Box 7)
    - Griffin, Wm. L. (Box 7)
    - Grimm, K.E. (Box 7)
    - Grose, Lucius T. (Box 7)
    - Gulbrandsen, Robt. (Box 7)
    - Gutierrez, Carlos (Box 7)
    - Gutierrez, Luis (Box 7)
    - Hahn, Peter M. (Box 7)
    - Hale, Chas. Martin (Box 7)
    - Hall, Clarence A. (Box 7)
    - Hall, Francis R. (Box 7)
    - Hermann, Siegfried (Box 7)
    - Hamilton, Douglas Holmes (Box 7)
    - Hamilton, E. L. (Box 7)
    - Harich, Jos. E. (Box 7)
    - Harris, Alan Paul (Box 7)
    - Harrison, P.H. (Box 7)
    - Hassan, Amin Ahmed (Box 7)
    - Hague, Carl John (Box 7)
    - Harenstrite, Stuart (Box 7)
    - Hayward, O.T. (Box 7)
    - Headlee, Larry Allyn (Box 7)
    - Hays, W.H. (Box 7)
    - Heckathorne, Theodore Allen (Box 7)
    - Hedberg, Jas. Dow (Box 7)
    - Heffelfinger, C.B. (Box 7)
    - Helgeson, Harold (Box 7)
    - Henderson, Frederick (Box 7)
    - Hendricks, I. D. (Box 7)
    - Henricksen, Donald (Box 7)
    - Herman, Theodore C. (Box 7)
    - Herrera, M.B. (Box 7)
    - Hill, Gill ma n A. (Box 7)
    - Hilton, Allan D. (Box 7)
    - Hites, H.J. (Box 7)
    - Hodges, James Clark (Box 7)
    - Hoffman, R.D. (Box 7)
    - Hogg, Stanley Luis (Box 7)
    - Hopson, Cliff A. (Box 7)
    - Hollister, Victor Frederick (Box 7)
    - Horton, Ogilvie J. (Box 7)
    - Hoskins, Cortez (Box 7)
    - Hughes, Judson B. (Box 7)
    - Hughes, Thos. A. (Box 7)
    - Hummel, Chas. L. (Box 7)
    - Hummel, Peter W. (Box 7)
    - Humphrey, Fred Jas. (Box 7)
    - Hurley, Neal L. (Box 7)
    - Hubt, Waldon Durand (Box 7)
    - Ibanez, Cesar (Box 7)
    - Inman, Will. U. (Box 7)
    - Ishikawa, Robt. (Box 7)
    - Jaafari-Tehrani, Aman-Ollah (Box 7)
    - Jackson, Everett Dale (Box 7)
    - Jager, Alan R. (Box 7)
    - Jager, M. Bond (Box 7)
    - Jarvis, D. (Box 7)
    - Javeri, Yusuf Alibbai (Box 7)
    - Jennings, Jos. Paul III (Box 7)
    - Jewett, John F. (Box 7)
    - Johnson, Grace P. (Box 7)
    - Johnston, Alan R. (Box 7)
    - Jones, Dale Eben (Box 7)
    - Jones, David L. (Box 7)
    - Jones, Vern (Box 7)
    - Jones, Wm. Riley (Box 7)
    - Jue, Jun Wan (Box 7)
    - Kafescioglu, Ismail A. (Box 7)
    - Kafescioglu, Nurtem (Mrs.) (Box 7)
    - Kanaya, Taro (Box 7)
    - Katz, Rosa (Box 7)
    - Keeler, Wm. S. (Box 7)
    - Keely, Russel D. (Box 7)
    - Kelly, F. R. (Box 7)
    - Kent, Bion H. (Box 7)
    - Kent, Harry C. (Box 7)
    - King, Barbara Jean (Box 7)
    - Kistler, Robt. B. (Box 7)
    - Klapper, Gilbert J. (Box 7)
    - Klink, H.N. (Box 7)
    - Knosher, J.E. (Box 7)
    - Knowles, Gerald (Box 7)
    - Knutson, C.F. (Box 7)
    - Krein, Frank P. (Box 7)
    - Krotz, Douglas R. (Box 7)
    - Kuepper, Klaus (Box 7)
    - Kvenvolden, Keith A. (Box 7)
    - Laak, Frank E. (Box 7)
    - Laak, John J. (Box 7)
    - Lagerquist, Thos. Edwin (Box 7)
    - Langan, Leon V. (Box 7)
    - Langerfeldt, Hans C. (Box 7)
    - Lao, Chester (Box 7)
    - LaPerle, G.R. (Box 7)
    - Latham, R.M. (Box 7)
    - Latker, Mark (Box 7)
    - Laue, Herbert Otto (Box 7)
    - Lawton, John (Box 7)
    - Laylander, P.A. (Box 7)
    - Lee, Donald E. (Box 7)
    - Lee, James (Box 7)
    - Leef, Jaren Forest (Box 7)
    - Lehman, Norman E. (Box 7)
    - Leo, Gerhard W. (Box 7)
    - Leon, Hernan J. (Box 7)
    - Leonard, Benjamin F. (Box 7)
    - Lessard, Robt. H. (Box 7)
    - Levorsen, John A. (Box 7)
    - Lewis, Carl Philip (Box 7)
    - Lewis, J.L. (Box 7)
    - Lewis, Jack R. (Box 7)
    - Lewis, Miles B. (Box 7)
    - Lewis, R. Q. (Box 7)
    - Lewis, R.W. Jr. (Box 8)
    - Lindauer, A.S. (Box 8)
    - Kindskog, Stanley V. (Box 8)
    - Lindval, Chas. (Box 8)
    - Lipman, Weldman Peter (Box 8)
    - Llewellyn, D. (Box 8)
    - Lofgren, Gary Ernest (Box 8)
    - Long, Bob (Box 8)
    - Long, C.E. (Box 8)
    - Loomis, Alden A. (Box 8)
    - Loskamp, Alvin N. (Box 8)
    - Loskamp, Harry K. (Box 8)
    - Lounsbury, R.W. (Box 8)
    - Lovely, Lummie C. (Box 8)
    - Lowe, Donald Ray (Box 8)
    - Lowell, J. David (Box 8)
    - Lund, Lamar (Box 8)
    - Lund, Wm. Sterling (Box 8)
    - OaLuz, Acyr Avila (Box 8)
    - McAfee, Robt. Jr. (Box 8)
    - McCarthy, James (Box 8)
    - McCloskey, D. (Box 8)
    - McCollom, Robt. L. (Box 8)
    - McDonald, Alex Chas. (Box 8)
    - McElheny, Richard (Box 8)
    - McHenry, John (Box 8)
    - McKay, Chas. W. (Box 8)
    - McKee, Elliot B. (Box 8)
    - McLeod, E. (Box 8)
    - McGirk, L.S. (Box 8)
    - MacLeod, G. M. (Box 8)
    - McMahon, Wm. G. (Box 8)
    - McWilliams, Robt. Gene (Box 8)
    - Maag, Harold Richard, Jr. (Box 8)
    - MacDiarmid, Roy A. (Box 8)
    - Mack, Erick John, Jr. (Box 8)
    - Mackevett, Edward (Box 8)
    - Maddox, Eleanor Jean (Box 8)
    - Madill, W. H. (Box 8)
    - Mahrholz, W.W. (Box 8)
    - Mandra, York T. (Box 8)
    - Manrique, Alberto (Box 8)
    - Mapes, E. V. (Box 8)
    - Marchand, Dennis Eugene (Box 8)
    - Marsh, Owen T. (Box 8)
    - Martin, Lewis (Box 8)
    - Martinez, Anibal R. (Box 8)
    - Martinez, Ruben (Box 8)
    - Mason, Hugh C. (Box 8)
    - Mau, F.A. (Box 8)
    - Mauldin, John S. (Box 8)
    - May, T. E. (Box 8)
    - Meade, Robt. H. (Box 8)
    - Medaris, Levi Gordon (Box 8)
    - Mederos H, Alfredo (Box 8)
    - Mejia, Victor M (Box 8)
    - Melendres, Medinacelli Mariano (Box 8)
    - Menzie, Thos. E. (Box 8)
    - Merchant, Steven Lee (Box 8)
    - Merrick, Robt. J. (Box 8)
    - Meyer, Robt. (Box 8)
    - Meyerhoff, A. (Box 8)
    - Militante, Priscilla J. (Box 8)
    - Miller, Albert B. (Box 8)
    - Miller, Chas. P. (Box 8)
    - Miller, Clarence A. (Box 8)
    - Miller, Kenneth Jos. (Box 8)
    - Miller, R.D. (Box 8)
    - Milow, E. Dean (Box 8)
    - Minard, Claude R. (Box 8)
    - Mitchell, S.D. (Box 8)
    - Modin, Roy Harold (Box 8)
    - Monson, Kenneth John (Box 8)
    - Montgomery, Edw. S. (Box 8)
    - Moore, Geo. W. (Box 8)
    - Moore, J.G. (Box 8)
    - Moreno-Agreda, Francisco (Box 8)
    - Morris, Eliot C. (Box 8)
    - Mcirris, Sheldon Allan (Box 8)
    - Morris, Spencer R. (Box 8)
    - Morshead, J.S. (Box 8)
    - Mowat, Geo. D. (Box 8)
    - Munasinghe, N.T.K. (Box 8)
    - Mundt, Philip A. (Box 8)
    - Mursky, Gregory A. (Box 8)
    - Na Chiengmai, Phong Phan (Box 8)
    - Nagel, Raymond H. (Box 8)
    - Naimi Ali Ibrahim (Box 8)
    - Narasunhan, Tyagarajan (Box 8)
    - Natera, Brigido R. (Box 8)
    - Natera, Maria M. (Box 8)
    - Neel, Wm. Henry (Box 8)
    - Neff, Coleen Lois (Box 8)
    - Nelson, Edw. W. (Box 8)
    - Netelbeek, Theodoor (Box 8)
    - Nicolaysen, Gerald (Box 8)
    - Nicolette, Robt. A. (Box 8)
    - Nisbet, Grant A. (Box 8)
    - Nisbet, John M. (Box 8)
    - Noble, Donald Chas. (Box 8)
    - Norbeck, Carl S. (Box 8)
    - Norbury, Cedri c (Box 8)
    - Norris, Robt. L. (Box 8)
    - Nutter, Neill H. (Box 8)
    - O'Connor, Thomas E. (Box 1)
    - Off, Theodore (Box 1)
    - Ojakangas, Richard W. (Box 1)
    - Ojeda, Jesus R. (Box 1)
    - Olander, Harvey C. (Box 1)
    - O'Malley, F. W. (Box 1)
    - Osborn, Sabra H. (Box 1)
    - Otis, John Wilson (Box 1)
    - Oyama, K~tura (Box 1)
    - Oyarzun, Jorge tv!. (Box 1)
    - Ozbek, Ertugrul (Box 1)
    - Packard, John T. (Box 1)
    - Pampeyan, Earl Haig (Box 1)
    - Paredes, Manuel (Box 1)
    - Park, Allan (Box 1)
    - Parker, R. L. (Box 1)
    - Parsons, Geoffrey III (Box 1)
    - Parsons, W.H. (Box 1)
    - Patri, Chitta Ranjan (Box 1)
    - Patton, Wm. W. (Box 1)
    - Payne, Anthony L. (Box 1)
    - Pearson, J.C. (Box 1)
    - Peel, Frederick A. (Box 1)
    - Peebles, Juan Frederico (Box 1)
    - Peers, Roi N. (Box 1)
    - Peirson, Abel (Box 1)
    - Pencall, Robt. B. (Box 1)
    - Perez, Ernesto (Box 1)
    - Perez-Lizano, Agustin F. (Box 1)
    - Persons, Philip E. (Box 1)
    - Peters, Frederick M. (Box 1)
    - Petersen, Carl Frank (Box 1)
    - Peterson, WIn. D. (Box 1)
    - Pewe, T.L. (Box 1)
    - Philips, Richard (Box 1)
    - Phoenix, David A. (Box 1)
    - Pick, Michael (Box 1)
    - Pickering, Ranard J. (Box 1)
    - Pierce, Kenneth Lee (Box 1)
    - Playford, Philip E. (Box 1)
    - Pollard, Dalton L. (Box 1)
    - Pomeroy, Russ A. (Box 1)
    - Porraz-Zanabria, A.R. (Box 1)
    - Porter, L. P. (Box 1)
    - Postle, Gordon L. (Box 1)
    - Pratt, S.F. (Box 1)
    - Pratt, Walden (Box 1)
    - Prano, Juan Antonio (Box 1)
    - Prothro, Joe Nelson (Box 1)
    - Puckett, James (Box 1)
    - Putnam, Bruce M. (Box 1)
    - Rael, Jose L. (Box 1)
    - Randau, John A. (Box 1)
    - Randau, Paul C. (Box 1)
    - Rankin, Rodney R. (Box 1)
    - Read, J. L, Jr. (Box 1)
    - Record, W. (Box 1)
    - Redmond, John L. (Box 1)
    - Reese, Jos. M. (Box 1)
    - Reeves, Elaine Louise (Box 1)
    - Reich, Lawrence Allan (Box 1)
    - Reid, E.F. (Box 1)
    - Reiser, Hillard M. (Box 1)
    - Renault, Jacques R. (Box 1)
    - Rendon-Cano, Federico (Box 1)
    - Rex, Robt. W. (Box 1)
    - Ribeiro-Filho, Evaristo (Box 1)
    - Richmond, James (Box 1)
    - Rickert, John E. (Box 1)
    - Riley, Francis Stevenson (Box 1)
    - Riva, John (Box 1)
    - Rivera, Antonio M. (Box 1)
    - Rivera, Rosalvina (Box 1)
    - Robinson, Gray (Box 1)
    - Robinson, M. L. (Box 1)
    - Rodriguez, Eduardo (Box 1)
    - Rodriguez, G. (Box 1)
    - Roehl, Perry O. (Box 1)
    - Rofe, Rafael (Box 1)
    - Rhodes, Robt. S. (Box 1)
    - Rojas, Gustavo (Box 1)
    - Rosa, Hermenegildo (Box 1)
    - Rosales, Hugo (Box 1)
    - Roscoe, S.M. (Box 1)
    - Rosenblum, S. (Box 1)
    - Rowland, Richard E. (Box 1)
    - Rudis, James Allan (Box 1)
    - Rupp, Gerald Eldor (Box 1)
    - Rutter, Nathaniel W. (Box 1)
    - Sadighi, Soleiman (Box 1)
    - Sagaser, Kendall Wayne (Box 1)
    - Saint-Leger, Yves (Box 1)
    - Salas, Raul O. (Box 1)
    - Saleem, Abdul S. (Box 1)
    - Samsoe, Soetrisno (Box 1)
    - Sanborn, A. F. (Box 1)
    - Sandburg, Chas. A. (Box 1)
    - Santos-Ynigo, Luis M. (Box 1)
    - Sandvik, Peter O. (Box 1)
    - Sater, James L. (Box 1)
    - Saunders, E. W. (Box 1)
    - Saunders, N.E. (Box 1)
    - Scheidecker, Wm. (Box 1)
    - Schell, Wm. F. (Box 1)
    - Schillinger, Alvin W. (Box 1)
    - Schilling, Frederick A. (Box 1)
    - Schmidt, E. (Box 1)
    - Schmidt, Eugene (Box 2)
    - Schmidt, Otto M. (Box 2)
    - Scholl, Dorothy (Box 2)
    - Schutz, Donald F. (Box 2)
    - Schweitzer, J. (Box 2)
    - Scudder, G.D. (Box 2)
    - Scarby, Edw. P. (Box 2)
    - Schuman, Richard Luther (Box 2)
    - Secor, Donald Terry (Box 2)
    - Seetharam, R. (Box 2)
    - Seilacher, Adolf (Box 2)
    - Shawe, D.R. (Box 2)
    - Sheldon, Richard P. (Box 2)
    - Shimazaki, Y. (Box 2)
    - Shklanka, Roman (Box 2)
    - Shiobara, Kanji (Box 2)
    - Showler, Wm. Y. (Box 2)
    - Simms, John S. (Box 2)
    - Sisler, John J. (Box 2)
    - Sithamparapillai, P.M. (Box 2)
    - Slavin, R.L. (Box 2)
    - Slough, David A. (Box 2)
    - Smith, David D. (Box 2)
    - Smith, Lee Anderson (Box 2)
    - Smith, Robt. J. (Box 2)
    - Sokol, Daniel (Box 2)
    - Soliman, Soliman M. (Box 2)
    - Sorensen, Glenn E. (Box 2)
    - Speyer, David L. (Box 2)
    - Speed, Robt. Clarke (Box 2)
    - Spitznas, Roger L. (Box 2)
    - Spotts, J.H. (Box 2)
    - Spresser, Ralph Gerald (Box 2)
    - Spurck, Walter H. (Box 2)
    - de Chadenedes, J.F. (Box 2)
    - Stallings, Laurence T. III (Box 2)
    - Stauffer, Karl W. (Box 2)
    - Stewart, John H. (Box 2)
    - Stice, Gary D. (Box 2)
    - Stieff, L. R. (Box 2)
    - Stone, John G. (Box 2)
    - Strom, Robt. (Box 2)
    - Stuart, David Johnson (Box 2)
    - Sutton, Don W. (Box 2)
    - Szatai, Janos (Box 2)
    - Taber, Bond (Box 2)
    - Tabor, Rowland (Box 2)
    - Taft, Wm. Harrison (Box 2)
    - Tagg, Richard A. (Box 2)
    - Tamesis, Emmanuel V. (Box 2)
    - Tailleur, Irvin L. (Box 2)
    - Taranik, James V. (Box 2)
    - Tarrico, Geo. John (Box 2)
    - Tarshis, Andrew L. (Box 2)
    - Tavera, E. (Box 2)
    - Taylor, Cecil McDow (Box 2)
    - Taylor, Edw. J. (Box 2)
    - Taylor, Lyman W. (Box 2)
    - Taylor, Samuel (Box 2)
    - Taylor, Sanford Allen (Box 2)
    - Tellez-Rocha, Abraham (Box 2)
    - Ten Eyck, Warren E. (Box 2)
    - Terry, Judith S. (Box 2)
    - Thacker, Michael M. (Box 2)
    - Thamer, D.C. (Box 2)
    - Thamer, Dugald H. (Box 2)
    - Theirs, Rene (Box 2)
    - Thompson, Thomas L. (Box 2)
    - Thomson, John N. (Box 2)
    - Thomson, Peter R. (Box 2)
    - Tippy, Roger Wm. (Box 2)
    - Tippett, Michael C. (Box 2)
    - Tolle, H. Edw. (Box 2)
    - de Ja Torre, A. (Box 2)
    - Touring, R.M. (Box 2)
    - Townsend, Harrison (Box 2)
    - Travers, Wm. B. (Box 2)
    - Trimingham, Robt. James (Box 2)
    - Tsai, Bruce K.H. (Box 2)
    - Tschanz, C.M. (Box 2)
    - Turner, Alice Mary (Box 2)
    - Vagliente, Victor (Box 2)
    - Van Denburgh, Albert (Box 2)
    - Van Nort, Steven D. (Box 2)
    - Vaughey, Wm. Meacher (Box 2)
    - Vaughan, R.H. (Box 2)
    - Verdejo, Cecilia (Box 2)
    - Ver Planck, W.E. (Box 2)
    - Vigrass, Lawrence W. (Box 2)
    - Villaneva, Louis F. (Box 2)
    - Vincelette, Richard Roy (Box 2)
    - Vogel, John D. (Box 2)
    - Voigt, Janice (Box 2)
    - Volbrecht, S.G. (Box 2)
    - Vonderosten, E. (Box 2)
    - Wagner, Frances (Box 2)
    - Waldron, John F. (Box 2)
    - Wallace, James A. (Box 2)
    - Wallace, Wm. F. (Box 2)
    - Walters, Richard F. (Box 2)
    - Ward, Hector J. (Box 2)
    - Warne, John R. (Box 2)
    - Weber, Paul W. (Box 3)
    - Weightman, Ivan M. (Box 3)
    - Weimer, Robt. J. (Box 3)
    - West, Michael Hatfield (Box 3)
    - Westheimer, Beverly Rose (Box 3)
    - Wheaton, R. O. (Box 3)
    - Wheeler, Chas. (Box 3)
    - Whelan, Peter (Box 3)
    - White, Langdon (Box 3)
    - White, R.M. (Box 3)
    - Whitten, Harold L. (Box 3)
    - Whittier, Donald (Box 3)
    - Wieman, John Philip (Box 3)
    - Wiester, John L. (Box 3)
    - Wiggins, John, Jr. (Box 3)
    - Wilckens, A.C. (Box 3)
    - Wilden, Chas. R. (Box 3)
    - Willet, Chas. R. (Box 3)
    - Williams, Lawrence R. (Box 3)
    - Willis, D.G. (Box 3)
    - Wilson, Edw. C. (Box 3)
    - Wilson, Francis C. (Box 3)
    - Wilson, James R. (Box 3)
    - Wilson, Richard F. (Box 3)
    - Wilson, Rod (Box 3)
    - Winchell, Robt. E. (Box 3)
    - Wise, Wm. Stewart (Box 3)
    - Wolfgang, Hugh (Box 3)
    - Wood, Edw. T. (Box 3)
    - Wood, James (Box 3)
    - Worley, David E. (Box 3)
    - Wright, Thos. L. (Box 3)
    - Wrucke, Chester (Box 3)
    - Yates, R.G. (Box 3)
    - Young, Janet E. (Box 3)
    - Zevallos, Francisco (Box 3)
  - Departmental minutes, 1922-1973
    - Department Minutes, Circa 1922-1972 (Box 4)
    - Krauskopf's comments on Dept. minutes. (Box 4)
    - American Geological Institute (1954-1959) (Box 4)
    - California Fund for Horticultural Research (4/54-8/64), 1954-1964 (Box 4)
  - Student record cards, 1907-1913
    - Anderson, Robert Edwin (Box 3)
    - Andreen, Harry Mayo (Box 3)
    - Andresen, Ludwig Paul (Box 3)
    - Arrell, Dell Bernie (Box 3)
    - Barton, Miller Dodge (Box 3)
    - Bayly, George Harold (Box 3)
    - Boyd, Harold Edward (Box 3)
    - Burris, Arthur Frederick (Box 3)
    - Chapin, Harold Addison (Box 3)
    - Clark, Douglas (Box 3)
    - Cooper, Warren Gosselin (Box 3)
    - Corbet, Edward Burke (Box 3)
    - Crandall, Darrell (Box 3)
    - Danielson, Arthur Frederick (Box 3)
    - Decius, Louis Courtney (Box 3)
    - Doheny, Edward Lawrence (Box 3)
    - Dunlap, Willard Everett (Box 3)
    - Erb, Benjamin Edward (Box 3)
    - Forbes, Frederick Brodie (Box 3)
    - Forbes, James Hyde (Box 3)
    - Fox, Philip Benton (Box 3)
    - Fyfe, Andrew Douglas (Box 3)
    - Garner, Aubrey Hamilton (Box 3)
    - Gehrman, William Conrad (Box 3)
    - Gilman, Walter Devereux (Box 3)
    - Hall, Elwin Benoni (Box 3)
    - Hall, Mortimer Louis (Box 3)
    - Hall, Mortimer Louis (Box 3)
    - Hammon, Wendell C. (Box 3)
    - Hannibal, Harold Briggs (Box 3)
    - Hayes, Francis William (Box 3)
    - Henry, Albert R. (Box 3)
    - Hilby, George Robert (Box 3)
    - Hirst, William Basil (Box 3)
    - Holden, Henry Ambrose (Box 3)
    - Humphrey, Harry Frank (Box 3)
    - Hunley, John Berdell (Box 3)
    - Hunter, Frank Caughey (Box 3)
    - Kassebaum, Henry Adams (Box 3)
    - Kuder, Clyde S. (Box 3)
    - Lantz, Grover Berner (Box 3)
    - Lasky, Bernard Harold (Box 3)
    - Lehr, Robert Phillip (Box 3)
    - Leib, Earl Russell Warren (Box 3)
    - McKenna, John Shore (Box 3)
    - McAleer, Charles Torrance (Box 3)
    - McCann, Robert James (Box 3)
    - McCray, Hugh Edgar (Box 3)
    - McNair, Stuart Strathy (Box 3)
    - Lyne, Henry Stephens (Box 3)
    - Luis, Franklin Alfred (Box 3)
    - Philippi, John Fred. (Box 3)
    - Setz, Helmuth Gustave (Box 3)
    - Shafer, Arthur J. (Box 3)
    - Shumway, Earl Jeremiah (Box 3)
    - Nobs, Walter Rudolf (Box 3)
    - Nolan, Edward Dana (Box 3)
    - Olmsted, Clarence Edward (Box 3)
    - Patterson, Lee (Box 3)
    - Paulsen, Jasper William (Box 3)
    - Ray, James Chandler (Box 3)
    - Reeves, Frank Wixon (Box 3)
    - Sevier, Milton W. (Box 3)
    - Simpson, Ralph Townsend (Box 3)
    - Sinclair, Ewart Gladstone (Box 3)
    - Skinner, John Kenneth (Box 3)
    - Soper, Ralph Hamilton (Box 3)
    - Stewart, Edwin John (Box 3)
    - Swem, Harry Archie (Box 3)
    - Thomas, Dan Horace (Box 3)
    - Thompson, Thomas West (Box 3)
    - Turner, Thomas Norton (Box 3)
    - Vrang, Christian Madsen (Box 3)
    - Wegis, Antone Henry (Box 3)
    - Whitted, James Herbert (Box 3)
    - Wickersham, Newton W. (Box 3)
    - Wright, Ernest Neall (Box 3)
    - Zinn, Cleo Jack (Box 3)
  - Student records, 1965-1975
    The materials are restricted 75 years from date of creation.
    - Aaron, William B (Box 13)
    - Abry, Claude H. (Box 13)
    - Amato, Francis L. (Box 13)
    - Anderson, (Nathanial) R. (Box 13)
    - Anderson, Mary F. (Box 13)
    - Anderson, David W. (Box 13)
    - Antonen, Gary J. (Box 13)
    - Angulo, Raul E. (Box 13)
    - Aruelles, (Mendoza) Victor (Box 13)
    - Arpat, Ali Essen (Box 13)
    - Ashely, Roger Parkmand (Box 13)
    - Atwater, Brian (Box 13)
    - Atwater, Richard W. (Box 13)
    - Austin, Michael G. (Box 13)
    - Avery, Cynthia (Box 13)
    - Awald, John (Box 13)
    - Babcock, Elizabeth M. (Box 13)
    - Bacon, Charles R. (Box 13)
    - Bahia, Tuimaraes, Paulo Fernando (Box 13)
    - Baldwin, Arthur D. (Box 13)
    - Ball, Gene R. (Box 13)
    - Ballow, Gary L. (Box 13)
    - Bamford, Robert W. (Box 13)
    - Bangs, Tracey R. (Box 13)
    - Barling, Albert A. (Box 13)
    - Barker, Judith A. (Box 13)
    - Bartlo, Peter A. (Box 13)
    - Bartow, John A. (Box 13)
    - Beaudoim, Gerald J. (Box 13)
    - Bela, James L. (Box 13)
    - Beaulieu, Alexander C. (Box 13)
    - Bergo, Edward T. G. (Box 13)
    - Bernstein, Neil S. (Box 13)
    - Berry, Anne L. (Box 13)
    - Bilzi, Paul A. (Box 13)
    - Bittencourt, N. O. (Box 13)
    - Blaisdell, Thomas F. (Box 13)
    - Blencoe, James G. (Box 13)
    - Bostick, Neely (Box 13)
    - Boyd, Harry R. (Box 13)
    - Brock, Kenneth J. (Box 13)
    - Buangan, Antonio (Box 13)
    - Burke, Dennis B. (Box 13)
    - Burt, Robert J. (Box 13)
    - Cameron, Bruce E. (Box 13)
    - Campbell, Robert w. (Box 13)
    - Carlson, Carl A. (Box 13)
    - Carlson, William D. (Box 13)
    - Carpenter, Robert A. (Box 13)
    - Carson, William P. (Box 13)
    - Carter, Claire (Box 13)
    - Cary, Michael J. (Box 13)
    - Casey, Tom Ann L. (Box 13)
    - Chang-Say Alfonson E. (Box 13)
    - Chilps, Stuart W. (Box 13)
    - Chipping, David H. (Box 13)
    - Clarke, Denis E. (Box 14)
    - Clark, Joseph C. (Box 14)
    - Clar, Malcolm M. (Box 14)
    - Close, Philip H. (Box 14)
    - Cocco, Michael L. (Box 14)
    - Cofer, Charles R. (Box 14)
    - Collinson, James W. (Box 14)
    - Conn, Carolyn M. (Box 14)
    - Cowan, Darrel S. (Box 14)
    - Crawford, Lawrence G. (Box 14)
    - Critlenden, Elizabeth A. (Box 14)
    - Cummings, J. C. (Box 14)
    - Cunningham, Charles G. (Box 14)
    - Dahl, Peter B. (Box 14)
    - Daboll, Joan (Box 14)
    - Dale, Diane C. (Box 14)
    - Dale, Ruth L. (Box 14)
    - Donnemiller, Robert E. (Box 14)
    - Darling, Richard G. (Box 14)
    - Darwish, Mostafa H. (Box 14)
    - Davies, Hugh Lucius (Box 14)
    - De le Cruz, Louis (Box 14)
    - Deminmen, Ferrah (Box 14)
    - De Nault, Kenneth J. (Box 14)
    - Enciso De la Vega, Salvador (Box 14)
    - Demont, Christina M. (Box 14)
    - Denton, Ross H. (Box 14)
    - Dickert (Taylor), Paul F. (Box 14)
    - Doll, Barry F. (Box 14)
    - Donnelly, Michael F. (Box 14)
    - Dohrenwend, John (Box 14)
    - Dowsett, Frederick R. (Box 14)
    - Dowty, Eric (Box 14)
    - Duffield, Wendell A. (Box 14)
    - Dymet, Robert F. (Box 14)
    - Ebet, Janet (Box 14)
    - Edverton, Alvin T. (Box 14)
    - Edwards, Jeffrey J. (Box 14)
    - Egemeir, Stephen J. (Box 14)
    - Ehret, Gayle A. (Box 14)
    - Eichelberger, John C. (Box 14)